I don't see it...
Sorry about this, Ishikawa-kun.
Nah, don't sweat it.
You dropped it around here, right?
Yes.
I just wish I could help you look...
Wobble Wobble Wobble
Don't worry! Just stay there where it's safe!
You bought some glasses, broke them,
and now you've dropped your contact...
You should eat more blueberries.
Yeah.
If it doesn't turn up, don't worry about it.
You must be getting cold.
We gotta help each other when we need it.
He's kneeling?!
Kneeling...?!
What the heck is happening here?
Did Yanagi-kun do something to Ishikawa-kun?
I need to tell them that
it's time to go home.
And then... ask what's going on.
He's glaring...
RUMMMBLE
Found it!
Thank you!
Just don't drop it again!
Hey, was someone there a second ago?
I think so, but I couldn't really tell.
Whoever it was ran away.
That's weird.
Student Council
Sengoku-kun, did you make sure
everything's locked up?
I'm sorry, Father. I couldn't make
the first move against Yanagi-kun.
Sengoku-kun?
Yanagi-kun missed our elective class today.
Did he?
Yanagi-kun
It's my only chance with him during the day.
Chance for what?
Come to think of it, he's absent
for a lot of morning classes.
Maybe he has trouble waking up.
Maybe.
Akane!
See you tomorrow!
Right!
Hori-san, now's your daily Yanagi-kun chance.
Hori-san?
Why...
Huh?
Why are you calling Yanagi-kun
by his first name?!
Um, I...
I'm sorry!
Like you're the best of friends...
I mean, I call him by his first name,
but it doesn't mean anything...
I want to call him by his first name, too!
Wait, that's what this is?
Do you think Yanagi-kun would mind
if I asked to call him by his first name?
I doubt it.
Y-You think so?
Really?
Weirdo.
Don't be like that. I'm just happy.
Kyon-Kyon, have you seen Yanagin?
He just left.
What?
But I brought these cookies for him...
Want them, Kyon-Kyon?
Sorry, I'm full.
That's too bad. Sakura made them.
Really?!
So what if she did?
Gimme!
No way.
Come on! Just a few!
This sucks.
The bus is running super late.
And I'm super in a hurry. It super sucks.
Super same. For real.
What's wrong, Miyamura?
Sounds like the bus is super,
super, super, super, super late.
That late?
I think Akane commutes by bus.
And it's really windy today.
The bus hasn't come yet.
It's cold.
Yo there, you all by your lonesome?
Bus Stop
Katagiri High School
Oh, erm, did you mean me?
Ayasaki-san?
Nope, I'm not Remi.
What are you doing?
Hitting on you.
Hitting on me?!
Gotta say, you're a cute one.
If you're down, wanna hang with me?
Should I?
Is she playing some kind of game?
Hey, back off. You're
bothering the poor thing.
You should know when you're not wanted.
Hori-san?
No, I'm just someone who, uh...
Someone passing by.
Oh, so you're not solo.
That's it. I'm outta here.
That's enough out of you, lowlife.
You—
Oh, sorry, you go ahead.
You sure?
Sorry, I, uh...
We forgot the next line,
so we're skipping it.
I see.
Hey, I heard at school that the bus
is gonna be fifteen minutes late.
Oh, really?
You got it.
And it's a cold one today.
So they came to let me know.
Thank you. If it's just fifteen
minutes, I can wait it out.
Heya.
I got 'em!
What took you?
Want some hot cocoa, Yanagin?
Huh?
Here.
Hey, they're all hot cocoa!
I figured no one would fight
if it was all the same.
Say, did you get one for me?
Y...a... Y...a... Yanagi-kun,
we brought cookies, too.
"Y...a... Y...a..."?
Thank you.
It's so warm! Thank you!
Kono-san made them. They're really good.
It's freezing today.
Thank you. Um, I...
Miyamura-kun, do you like hot cocoa?
No one likes waiting in the cold all alone.
It feels really good in winter.
Am I right?
I know, right?
O-Or are we bothering you?
We can head back to school—
No, not at all!
A text?
From my dad.
He was excited about coming home
early so we could all go out to eat.
Dad
Should I come get you?
You know, Yanagin...
It was Miyamura-kun's idea
to get you something warm to drink.
Ayasaki-san, where did you
get those sunglasses?
The student council room.
Whose are they?!
Oh, sorry! I ate five cookies by myself!
I should've brought my coat today.
Me, too.
You girls must already be cold
with your legs exposed.
No need. I'm with my friends
You could try a skirt, Miyamura.
Why?!
Hori-san, I'd like a cookie, please.
Here!
Thank you.
I've heard that certain students
have been skipping elective classes
because they're frequently self-study hall.
This is an important time of year.
You must use the remainder of it wisely!
Therefore...
I will not permit any tardiness among
the students of class 3-6 next week!
Understood?!
Yes, ma'am.
When Sengoku sends a text,
sometimes I wonder if it's really him.
I get that.
Why?! I send perfectly normal texts!
Yuki wants to go to the zoo
Invite Ayasaki-san and Kouno-san along
<From Sengoku>
Tomorrow? Sure, I'm free. Why?
At first, sure.
Use kanji in your texts.
Okay. I think they'll go, too.
They start off perfectly normal.
I'll do what I want
You should try some cute faces in yours
Kyo-chan, I saw some water backflowing
all over the floor at school today—
Waa~ How stupid~
Do you feel no shame when texting?
Please stop going through those texts...
To be fair, sometimes when Miyamura
texts me, I feel like I'm talking to a girl.
You do?
What do you think, Yanagi?
THUD
Yanagi, did you just
hit your head on the desk?
Huh? What makes you think that?
Why would I hit my head on the desk?
He looks bleary-eyed.
Yanagi-kun, are you tired?
Did you sleep okay? Is something wrong?
Um, well... actually...
You can't be late for a week?
Like an anti-tardiness campaign?
That makes it sound like a good thing.
No, it doesn't.
I have trouble getting up, and I get
so nervous that I can't fall asleep.
Even one tardiness will get my name
and photo put up for everyone to see.
Terror...
Th-That's going too far.
Yanagi-kun is tardy a lot.
What if you go to bed early?
I tried, but I wake up at odd hours.
That's a vicious cycle.
But it's only for two more days,
so I'll tough it out.
Okay, but make sure you set your alarm clock.
Yeah, I've actually been setting two of them.
Oh, but one stopped yesterday,
so I barely made it on time today.
It just stopped?
No, I found it broken on the floor
across the room from my bed.
I don't remember moving it, though.
I discovered it when I got home.
My bed was a mess, too, but my parents
said they hadn't been in my room.
It's a little mysterious... and kinda freaky.
Sorry to jabber on so long.
I'm sure you don't care, right?
We do. Go on.
A sense for horror
But a supernatural phenomenon? I know you're
not hurt, but is that really okay?
You should carry salt on you!
Salt?
Hey, when you can't get up in the morning,
is it because of sleep paralysis?
No, I'm just sleepy.
Honest
It's totally up to you, but is one alarm
clock really going to be enough?
I could give you a wake-up call.
Hey, that's a good idea.
You should still set your alarm clock,
but I'll give you a call
to make sure you get up.
And you text him, Sengoku. It'll be funny.
Why's that?
Are you teasing me again?
I want to call him, too!
It's for Yanagi, okay?
But a text...?
I-I'm really not a morning person, so...
You can just hang up
without saying anything,
so long as the call wakes you up.
Thank you!
A text... A wake-up text...
This'll be fun.
I need to make sure I wake up tomorrow.
Yeah.
Yanagi
What? It's morning?
Can't be...
It's 1:30. It's still nighttime.
I'll go back to sleep.
Hey, Akane? Good morning! Are you up?
I'm not getting up.
Huh?
So tired...
Oh, Yanagi? Good morning.
You'd better get up or else—
Yanagi Akane, eighteen years old...
is incredibly bad at getting out of bed.
Oh, a text...
Sengoku-kun
I managed to get up!
Thank you all!
I'm glad, but getting hung up on without
a word definitely stung a little.
I-I'm sorry.
I was so tired that
I don't really remember...
Yanagi-kun.
Oh, Sengoku-kun, that text was really funny.
Funny?
Thank you.
Thought he was being serious
It really did the trick and woke me up.
Should we call you again tomorrow?
No, thanks. I'll be fine.
I have to learn to stand on my own.
Plus, I did hear my alarm go off.
Yeah? Let me know if you change your mind.
I will!
Yanagi wouldn't realize
until the next morning...
that his alarm clock was done for.
Warm
Can decide between green and oolong tea?
Yanagi-kun.
Low-Calorie Sports Drink
Sorry.
Th-That's quite all right.
I'm fine with anything.
I was just feeling a bit thirsty.
This one is brand new, isn't that right?
Yanagi-kun, you talk normally with
your classmates and Yoshikawa-san,
but you're so polite with the rest of us.
Just habit, I suppose.
I'm casual with my friends
and people I want to be friends with.
Oh.
I-It's not what you think! Really!
I didn't mean I don't want to be
friends with you guys!
The person I want to be friendlier with
doesn't even want to talk normally to me.
I'd at least like to be acknowledged as a
classmate. What if I never get to that point?
I just don't know. I can't even think straight.
I don't want to bother Yanagi-kun with
something like this, but I can't think anymore.
This is such a shock.
I don't know what to do.
It's too late!
Talk about a heavy mood!
Depressed
Wait, what's got Sengoku so down?
Sengoku-san, what's up?
Is something the matter?
You can tell your pal Iura!
Y'know, get it off your chest!
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Buzz off.
Sengoku!
Okay, that's on Shu for being obnoxious.
I am not!
Did something happen with Ayasaki?
I got dumped.
Shu, Ayasaki's single now!
Not by Remi! By Yanagi-kun!
Oh, so Yanagi dumped you.
I thought you were getting along.
He said he's so polite with me
because he doesn't want to be friends.
Did he really...?
Yanagi, want half of this?
Oh, how kind of you.
I can't finish it on my own.
What is it?
A really sweet danish.
There's so much chocolate,
it gave me heartburn.
Is it good?
Yeah, I really dig it.
O-Oh, that's great. I'm glad.
Yes.
Why are you smirking
like you've won something?
You're not the only one
he's super polite with.
Yeah, don't let it bother you.
I know, but still...
Everyone, even Ayasaki, seems
awfully attracted to Yanagi.
Okay, I'll let it go. I'll treat him
the same way I always do.
So we're just friends...
What'd you want to be?
Warm
Oh.
S-Sengoku-kun.
Fresh Squeezed Juice Blend
I-I-I'm so sorry.
No, it's fine. I was having trouble deciding.
Oh, that doesn't look good.
Um, I'm sure I could drink it,
so why don't you give it to me?
I'll buy you another one,
so please drink that instead.
All right. Thank you.
Of course!
Here. I, um... Take this.
Thank you.
This juice has a unique taste, so lots of
kids in class don't like it, you know?
Is he trying to be more casual with me?
Sorry.
Huh?
You can talk to me however
you'd like. Don't force yourself.
O-O-Oh... Okay! I will!
Oh, good... I, uh, I'm glad.
2-4-6 Tea Blend
Oolong Tea
Warm
Sengoku's grossing me out.
What? Is he doing something weird?
Hey, you're right! Look at that grin!
SLAP
He slapped me!
Sengoku's pretty straightforward
with his feelings.
He probably made up with Yanagi.
Oh, hi, Yanagin!
Where are you off to?
I'm returning to the classroom.
Not so fast! I told you to be
casual with me, didn't I?
Hey, you're laughing me off!
If only I could play it
this straight with Sengoku-kun.
Oh, hi, Yanagin! Where are you off to?
Why are you being so stuffy?
I told you we're friends, didn't I?
No, Sengoku-kun's not like that!
Yanagin, are you gonna cry?
What's wrong?
I-I'm doing it, Iura-kun.
Yeah, bring it on, Akane!
Here goes.
What are you doing?
Hello, Ishikawa-kun and Sengoku-kun.
Iura-kun was saying he can
catch a blade with his hands.
Is that so?
I could've caught a katana if we had one.
You'd make a murderer of Yanagi?
You with me, Sengoku?
I wonder...
If I were to say I could catch a blade
between my hands like Iura-kun...
Would Yanagi do that to me, too?
Huh?
M-Maybe?
Yanagi-kun...
seems to attract cheerful people.
You mean airheads? Like Yoshikawa?
If air... If cheerful people are
easier for him to get along with,
I guess I don't stand a chance.
Why not be a cheerful airhead, then?
When I saw her the other day...
Hey, you're not listening, Sengoku.
Hey, that's Yoshikawa-san.
Ow!
I'm sorry!
She mistook the wall
for a person and apologized?
I do that sometimes, too.
There's more.
It's the first time I've seen
someone glare at a wall.
I don't think I can ever
be like Yoshikawa-san.
Okay, and...
Me either.
Take this!
You caught it?!
But if you acted more like Shu,
maybe you could be friendlier.
You want me to act like Iura-kun?
That's compromising too much!
I feel you, but he's better than Yoshikawa.
I'll show you what I mean. Just watch.
O-Okay.
Yanagi!
Yes?
Side attack!
Tickle
Akane's ticklish on
the soles of his feet, too!
Now you do it.
Me, do that?!
No! Nope! Never! No way! No how!
You idiot! You'll never
accomplish anything like that!
You want to be better friends
than before, don't you?!
than now, don't you?!
I need to practice first, Ishikawa-kun.
Why do you need a rehearsal?
There.
Grab
Stop! That was way too sensual!
That wasn't what I was expecting.
What's with you?
I don't have any idea.
Don't be mad.
It was like you were molesting me.
Seriously?
I'm glad we're rehearsing.
You're a molester, President?
Why do you pass by at
the worst possible times?!
Doing a little roleplay?
Yeah, and Sengoku's the molester.
Hey.
Then who are you, Ishikawa-kun?
Yanagi.
The casting's all wrong!
Are we on a train or something?!
So the scene's Akane
getting felt up on the train, huh?
Who should I be?
I only wish I could be as dumb as you.
He actually called someone dumb!
What's this all of a sudden? Bullying?
No.
Sengoku-kun wants to get closer with a friend.
What? We're all already good friends.
Is that not enough for him?
Am I the only one who thinks we're friends?!
Why do you look like your life's in danger?!
What's up?
You fighting?
I can't believe your timing!
The president's kicking me out!
What? The president's bullying someone?!
That's enough!
Sengoku-kun wouldn't do that.
Smile
You always take Sengoku-san's side.
D-Do I?
Sengoku and Yanagi really
are good friends, huh?
Could you be any more obvious?!
Yanagi, Sengoku says he wants to be Shu.
Huh? Why?
I like him the way he is.
What's this?! You want to be me?!
BEEEEAM
Let's start with a haircut!
I didn't mean the way you look!
First a molester, then Iura-kun...
Talk about a busy day, President.
Molester?
No! That was a misunderstanding!
Miyamura, come to the
student council room later!
Yammer
Huh? Why? What did I do?
I'm angry at you!
Huh? Why?
You should know already!
Miyamura-kun and Sengoku-kun
get along great, don't they?
You just caused a lot of confusion!
Next time
page.9 Teacher